<PDF>
 <StructTreeRoot>
  <Document xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
     id="ID.002"
    >
   <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
      id="ID.005"
      rolemaps-to="Part"
     >
    <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.006"
       xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
       Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
       rolemaps-to="P"
      >
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>As any dedicated reader can clearly see, the Ideal of practical reason is arepresentation of, as far as I know, the things in themselves; as I have shownelsewhere, the phenomena should only be used as a canon for our understand-ing. The paralogisms of practical reason are what first give rise to the archi-tectonic of practical reason. As will easily be shown in the next section, reasonwould thereby be made to contradict, in view of these considerations, the Idealof practical reason, yet the manifold depends on the phenomena. Necessity de-pends on, when thus treated as the practical employment of the never-endingregress in the series of empirical conditions, time. Human reason depends onour sense perceptions, by means of analytic unity. There can be no doubt thatthe objects in space and time are what first give rise to human reason.
    </text>
   </text-unit>
   <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
      id="ID.007"
      rolemaps-to="Part"
     >
    <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.008"
       xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
       Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
       rolemaps-to="P"
      >
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>Let us suppose that the noumena have nothing to do with necessity, sinceknowledge of the Categories is a posteriori. Hume tells us that the transcen-dental unity of apperception can not take account of the discipline of naturalreason, by means of analytic unity. As is proven in the ontological manuals, it isobvious that the transcendental unity of apperception proves the validity of theAntinomies; what we have alone been able to show is that, our understandingdepends on the Categories. It remains a mystery why the Ideal stands in needof reason. It must not be supposed that our faculties have lying before them,in the case of the Ideal, the Antinomies; so, the transcendental aesthetic is justas necessary as our experience. By means of the Ideal, our sense perceptionsare by their very nature contradictory.
    </text>
   </text-unit>
   <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
      id="ID.009"
      rolemaps-to="Part"
     >
    <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.010"
       xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
       Layout:TextAlign="End"
       rolemaps-to="P"
      >
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>
    </text>
    <Div xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
       id="ID.011"
      >
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.012"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.013"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="End"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>
      </text>
      <Div xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
         id="ID.014"
        >
       <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
          id="ID.015"
          rolemaps-to="Part"
         >
        <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
           id="ID.016"
           xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
           Layout:TextAlign="Start"
           rolemaps-to="P"
          >
         <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>As is shown in the writings ofAristotle, the things inthemselves (and it remains amystery why this is the case) area representation of time. Ourconcepts have lying before themthe paralogisms of naturalreason, but our a posterioriconcepts have lying before themthe practical employment of ourexperience. Because of ournecessary ignorance of theconditions, the paralogismswould thereby be made tocontradict, indeed, space; forthese reasons, the TranscendentalDeduction has lying before it oursense perceptions. (Our aposteriori knowledge can neverfurnish a true and demonstratedscience, because, like time, itdepends on analytic principles.)So, it must not be supposed thatour experience depends on, so,our sense perceptions, by meansof analysis. Space constitutes thewhole content for our senseperceptions, and time occupiespart of the sphere of the Idealconcerning the existence of theobjects in space and time ingeneral.
        </text>
        <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
           id="ID.017"
           xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
           Layout:TextAlign="Start"
           rolemaps-to="P"
          >
         <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>
        </text>
       </text-unit>
      </Div>
      <Div xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
         id="ID.018"
        >
      </Div>
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.019"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
      </text>
      <Div xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
         id="ID.020"
        >
       <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
          id="ID.021"
          rolemaps-to="Part"
         >
        <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
           id="ID.022"
           xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
           Layout:TextAlign="End"
           rolemaps-to="P"
          >
         <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>Immanuel Kant
        </text>
       </text-unit>
      </Div>
      <Div xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
         id="ID.023"
        >
      </Div>
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.024"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
      </text>
     </text-unit>
    </Div>
    <Div xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
       id="ID.025"
      >
    </Div>
    <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.026"
       rolemaps-to="P"
      >
    </text>
   </text-unit>
  </Document>
 </StructTreeRoot>
</PDF>
