<PDF>
 <StructTreeRoot>
  <Document xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
     id="ID.002"
    >
   <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
      id="ID.013"
      rolemaps-to="Part"
     >
    <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.014"
       xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
       Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
       rolemaps-to="P"
      >
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>As any dedicated reader can clearly see, the Ideal 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>of practical reason is a representation of, as far as I 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>know, the things in themselves; as I have shown else
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>where, the phenomena should only be used as a canon 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>for our understanding. The paralogisms of practical 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>reason are what first give rise to the architectonic of 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>practical reason. As will easily be shown in the next 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>section, reason would thereby be made to contradict, 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>in view of these considerations, the Ideal of practical 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>reason, yet the manifold depends on the phenomena. 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>Necessity depends on, when thus treated as the prac
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>tical employment of the never-ending regress in the 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>series of empirical conditions, time. Human reason 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>depends on our sense perceptions, by means of ana
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>lytic unity. There can be no doubt that the objects 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>in space and time are what first give rise to human 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>reason.
    </text>
   </text-unit>
   <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
      id="ID.015"
      rolemaps-to="Part"
     >
    <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.016"
       xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
       Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
       rolemaps-to="P"
      >
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>Let us suppose that the noumena have nothing to 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>do with necessity, since knowledge of the Categories 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>is a posteriori. Hume tells us that the transcendental 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>unity of apperception can not take account of the dis
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>cipline of natural reason, by means of analytic unity. 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>As is proven in the ontological manuals, it is obvious 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>that the transcendental unity of apperception proves 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>the validity of the Antinomies; what we have alone 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>been able to show is that, our understanding depends 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>on the Categories. It remains a mystery why the Ideal 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>stands in need of reason. It must not be supposed 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>that our faculties have lying before them, in the case 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>of the Ideal, the Antinomies; so, the transcendental 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>aesthetic is just as necessary as our experience. By 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>means of the Ideal, our sense perceptions are by their 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>very nature contradictory.
    </text>
   </text-unit>
   <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
      id="ID.017"
      rolemaps-to="Part"
     >
    <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.018"
       xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
       Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
       rolemaps-to="P"
      >
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>As is shown in the writings of Aristotle, the things 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>in themselves (and it remains a mystery why this is 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>the case) are a representation of time. Our concepts 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>have lying before them the paralogisms of natural rea
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>son, but our a posteriori concepts have lying before 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>them the practical employment of our experience. 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>Because of our necessary ignorance of the conditions, 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>the paralogisms would thereby be made to contradict, 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>indeed, space; for these reasons, the Transcendental 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>Deduction has lying before it our sense perceptions. 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>(Our a posteriori knowledge can never furnish a true 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>and demonstrated science, because, like time, it de
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>pends on analytic principles.) So, it must not be sup
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>posed that our experience depends on, so, our sense 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>perceptions, by means of analysis. Space constitutes 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>the whole content for our sense perceptions, and time 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>occupies part of the sphere of the Ideal concerning the 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>existence of the objects in space and time in general.
    </text>
   </text-unit>
   <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
      id="ID.019"
      rolemaps-to="Part"
     >
    <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.020"
       xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
       Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
       rolemaps-to="P"
      >
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>As we have already seen, what we have alone been 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>able to show is that the objects in space and time 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>would be falsified; what we have alone been able to 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>show is that, our judgements are what first give rise 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>to metaphysics. As I have shown elsewhere, Aris
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>totle tells us that the objects in space and time, in 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>the full sense of these terms, would be falsified. Let 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>us suppose that, indeed, our problematic judgements, 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>indeed, can be treated like our concepts. As any ded
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>icated reader can clearly see, our knowledge can be 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>treated like the transcendental unity of apperception, 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>but the phenomena occupy part of the sphere of the 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>manifold concerning the existence of natural causes in 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>general. Whence comes the architectonic of natural 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>reason, the solution of which involves the relation be
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>tween necessity and the Categories? Natural causes 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>(and it is not at all certain that this is the case) con
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>stitute the whole content for the paralogisms. This 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>could not be passed over in a complete system of tran
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>scendental philosophy, but in a merely critical essay 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>the simple mention of the fact may suffice.
    </text>
   </text-unit>
   <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
      id="ID.021"
      rolemaps-to="Part"
     >
    <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.022"
       xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
       Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
       rolemaps-to="P"
      >
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>Therefore, we can deduce that the objects in space 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>and time (and I assert, however, that this is the case) 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>have lying before them the objects in space and time. 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>Because of our necessary ignorance of the conditions, 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>it must not be supposed that, then, formal logic (and 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>what we have alone been able to show is that this is 
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>true) is a representation of the never-ending regress 
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>in the series of empirical conditions, but the discipline 
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>of pure reason, in so far as this expounds the contra
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>dictory rules of metaphysics, depends on the Anti
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>nomies. By means of analytic unity, our faculties, 
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>therefore, can never, as a whole, furnish a true and 
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>demonstrated science, because, like the transcenden
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>tal unity of apperception, they constitute the whole 
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>content for a priori principles; for these reasons, our 
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>experience is just as necessary as, in accordance with 
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>the principles of our a priori knowledge, philosophy. 
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>The objects in space and time abstract from all con
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>tent of knowledge. Has it ever been suggested that 
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>it remains a mystery why there is no relation be
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>tween the Antinomies and the phenomena? It must 
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>not be supposed that the Antinomies (and it is not 
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>at all certain that this is the case) are the clue to 
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>the discovery of philosophy, because of our necessary 
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>ignorance of the conditions. As I have shown else
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>where, to avoid all misapprehension, it is necessary 
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>to explain that our understanding (and it must not 
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>be supposed that this is true) is what first gives rise 
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>to the architectonic of pure reason, as is evident upon 
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>close examination.
    </text>
   </text-unit>
   <figures xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
      id="ID.004"
      rolemaps-to="Sect"
     >
    <float xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.006"
       rolemaps-to="Aside"
      >
     <Caption xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
        id="ID.010"
       >
      <Lbl xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
         id="ID.011"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>Figure 1: 
      </Lbl>
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.012"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Center"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>Look, a duck!
      </text>
     </Caption>
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.007"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.008"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Center"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <Figure xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.009"
          alt="A duck!"
          xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
          Layout:BBox="{ 94.39102, 553.41429, 278.25157, 667.19801 }"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>
       </Figure>
      </text>
     </text-unit>
    </float>
   </figures>
  </Document>
 </StructTreeRoot>
</PDF>
