<PDF>
 <StructTreeRoot>
  <Document xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
     id="ID.002"
    >
   <Sect xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
      id="ID.005"
     >
    <section xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.006"
       title="Without \texttt {linebreaker}"
       rolemaps-to="H1"
      >
     <section-number xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.007"
        rolemaps-to="Span"
       >
      <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>1 
     </section-number>
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>Without linebreaker
    </section>
    <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.008"
       rolemaps-to="Part"
      >
     <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.009"
        xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
        Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
        rolemaps-to="P"
       >
      <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>As any dedicated reader can clearly see, the Ideal of practical reason is a representation of, as far as I know, the things in themselves; as I have shown elsewhere, the phenomena should only be used as a canon for our understand­ing. The paralogisms of practi­cal reason are what first give rise to the architectonic of practical reason. As will easily be shown in the next section, reason would thereby be made to contradict, in view of these considerations, the Ideal of practical reason, yet the manifold depends on the phenom­ena. Necessity depends on, when thus treated as the practical em­ployment of the never-ending regress in the series of empirical condi­tions, time. Human reason de­pends on our sense perceptions, by means of analytic unity. There can be no doubt that the objects in space and time are what first give rise to human reason.
     </text>
    </text-unit>
   </Sect>
   <Sect xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
      id="ID.010"
     >
    <section xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.011"
       title="With \texttt {linebreaker}"
       rolemaps-to="H1"
      >
     <section-number xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.012"
        rolemaps-to="Span"
       >
      <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>2 
     </section-number>
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>With linebreaker
    </section>
    <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.013"
       rolemaps-to="Part"
      >
     <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.014"
        xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
        Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
        rolemaps-to="P"
       >
      <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>As any dedicated reader can clearly see, the Ideal of prac­tical reason is a representation of, as far as I know, the things in themselves; as I have shown elsewhere, the phenomena should only be used as a canon for our understanding. The paralogisms of practical reason are what first give rise to the architectonic of practical reason. As will easily be shown in the next section, rea­son would thereby be made to 
      <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>contradict, in view of these con­siderations, the Ideal of practi­cal reason, yet the manifold de­pends on the phenomena. Ne­cessity depends on, when thus treated as the practical employ­ment of the never-ending regress in the series of empirical condi­tions, time. Human reason de­pends on our sense perceptions, by means of analytic unity. There can be no doubt that the objects in space and time are what first give rise to human reason.
     </text>
    </text-unit>
   </Sect>
  </Document>
 </StructTreeRoot>
</PDF>
