<PDF>
 <StructTreeRoot>
  <Document xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
     id="ID.002"
    >
   <Sect xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
      id="ID.005"
     >
    <section xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.006"
       rolemaps-to="H1"
      >
     <section-number xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.007"
        rolemaps-to="Span"
       >
      <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>1 
     </section-number>
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>Some section
    </section>
    <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.008"
       rolemaps-to="Part"
      >
     <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.009"
        xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
        Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
        rolemaps-to="P"
       >
      <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>As any dedicated reader can clearly see, the Ideal of practical reason is a representation of, as far as I know, the things in themselves; as I have shown elsewhere, the phenomena should only be used as a canon for our under­standing. The paralogisms of practical reason are what first give rise to the architectonic of practical reason. As will easily be shown in the next sec­tion, reason would thereby be made to contradict, in view of these considera­tions, the Ideal of practical reason, yet the manifold depends on the phenom­ena. Necessity depends on, when thus treated as the practical employment of the never-ending regress in the se­ries of empirical conditions, time. Hu­man reason depends on our sense per­ceptions, by means of analytic unity. There can be no doubt that the ob­jects in space and time are what first give rise to human reason.
     </text>
    </text-unit>
    <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.010"
       rolemaps-to="Part"
      >
     <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.011"
        xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
        Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
        rolemaps-to="P"
       >
      <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>Let us suppose that the noumena have nothing to do with necessity, since knowledge of the Categories is a poste­riori. Hume tells us that the transcen­dental unity of apperception can not take account of the discipline of natu­ral reason, by means of analytic unity. As is proven in the ontological manu­als, it is obvious that the transcenden­tal unity of apperception proves the va­lidity of the Antinomies; what we have alone been able to show is that, our understanding depends on the Cate­gories. It remains a mystery why the Ideal stands in need of reason. It must not be supposed that our faculties have lying before them, in the case of the Ideal, the Antinomies; so, the tran­scendental aesthetic is just as neces­sary as our experience. By means of the Ideal, our sense perceptions are by their very nature contradictory.
     </text>
    </text-unit>
    <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.012"
       rolemaps-to="Part"
      >
     <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.013"
        xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
        Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
        rolemaps-to="P"
       >
      <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>some text
      <footnotemark xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.014"
         rolemaps-to="Lbl"
         referenced-as="2"
        >
        <?References objects="1" ?>
       <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>1
      </footnotemark>
      <footnote xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.015"
         rolemaps-to="FENote"
         referenced-as="1"
        >
        <?References objects="2" ?>
       <footnotelabel xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
          id="ID.018"
          rolemaps-to="Lbl"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>1
       </footnotelabel>
       <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
          id="ID.016"
          rolemaps-to="Part"
         >
        <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
           id="ID.017"
           xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
           Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
           rolemaps-to="P"
          >
         <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>some footnote
        </text>
       </text-unit>
      </footnote>
     </text>
    </text-unit>
   </Sect>
  </Document>
 </StructTreeRoot>
</PDF>
