<PDF>
 <StructTreeRoot>
  <Document xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
     id="ID.002"
    >
   <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
      id="ID.005"
      rolemaps-to="Part"
     >
    <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.006"
       xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
       Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
       rolemaps-to="P"
      >
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>text
     <footnotemark xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.007"
        rolemaps-to="Lbl"
        referenced-as="2"
       >
       <?References objects="1" ?>
      <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>1
     </footnotemark>
     <footnote xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.008"
        rolemaps-to="FENote"
        referenced-as="1"
       >
       <?References objects="2" ?>
      <footnotelabel xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.011"
         rolemaps-to="Lbl"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>1
      </footnotelabel>
      <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.009"
         rolemaps-to="Part"
        >
       <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
          id="ID.010"
          xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
          Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
          rolemaps-to="P"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>a footnote
       </text>
      </text-unit>
     </footnote>
    </text>
   </text-unit>
   <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
      id="ID.012"
      rolemaps-to="Part"
     >
    <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.013"
       xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
       Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
       rolemaps-to="P"
      >
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>more text
    </text>
    <Aside xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
       id="ID.014"
      >
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.015"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.016"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>a margin note
      </text>
     </text-unit>
    </Aside>
   </text-unit>
   <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
      id="ID.017"
      rolemaps-to="Part"
     >
    <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.018"
       xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
       Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
       rolemaps-to="P"
      >
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>As any dedicated reader can clearly see, the Ideal of practical reason is a representation of, as far as I know, the things in themselves; as I have shown elsewhere, the phenomena should only be used as a canon for our understand
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>ing. The paralogisms of practical rea
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>son are what first give rise to the ar
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>chitectonic of practical reason. As will easily be shown in the next section, rea
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>son would thereby be made to contra
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>dict, in view of these considerations, the Ideal of practical reason, yet the mani
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>fold depends on the phenomena. Neces
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>sity depends on, when thus treated as the practical employment of the never-ending regress in the series of empiri
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>cal conditions, time. Human reason de
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>pends on our sense perceptions, by means 
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>of analytic unity. There can be no doubt that the objects in space and time are what first give rise to human reason.
    </text>
   </text-unit>
   <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
      id="ID.019"
      rolemaps-to="Part"
     >
    <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.020"
       xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
       Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
       rolemaps-to="P"
      >
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>Let us suppose that the noumena have nothing to do with necessity, since knowl
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>edge of the Categories is a posteriori. Hume tells us that the transcendental unity of apperception can not take ac
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>count of the discipline of natural reason, by means of analytic unity. As is proven in the ontological manuals, it is obvious that the transcendental unity of apper
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>ception proves the validity of the Anti
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>nomies; what we have alone been able to show is that, our understanding de
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>pends on the Categories. It remains a mystery why the Ideal stands in need of reason. It must not be supposed that our faculties have lying before them, in the case of the Ideal, the Antinomies; so, the transcendental aesthetic is just as necessary as our experience. By means of the Ideal, our sense perceptions are 
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>by their very nature contradictory.
    </text>
   </text-unit>
   <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
      id="ID.021"
      rolemaps-to="Part"
     >
    <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.022"
       xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
       Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
       rolemaps-to="P"
      >
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>As is shown in the writings of Aris
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>totle, the things in themselves (and it remains a mystery why this is the case) are a representation of time. Our con
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>cepts have lying before them the paral
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>ogisms of natural reason, but our a pos
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>teriori concepts have lying before them the practical employment of our expe
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>rience. Because of our necessary igno
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>rance of the conditions, the paralogisms would thereby be made to contradict, indeed, space; for these reasons, the Tran
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>scendental Deduction has lying before it our sense perceptions. (Our a pos
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>teriori knowledge can never furnish a true and demonstrated science, because, like time, it depends on analytic prin
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>ciples.) So, it must not be supposed that our experience depends on, so, our sense perceptions, by means of analy
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>sis. Space constitutes the whole content for our sense perceptions, and time oc
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>
     <?MarkedContent page="4" ?>cupies part of the sphere of the Ideal concerning the existence of the objects in space and time in general.
    </text>
   </text-unit>
   <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
      id="ID.023"
      rolemaps-to="Part"
     >
    <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.024"
       xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
       Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
       rolemaps-to="P"
      >
     <?MarkedContent page="4" ?>As we have already seen, what we have alone been able to show is that the objects in space and time would be fal
     <?MarkedContent page="4" ?>sified; what we have alone been able to show is that, our judgements are what first give rise to metaphysics. As I have shown elsewhere, Aristotle tells us that the objects in space and time, in the full sense of these terms, would be fal
     <?MarkedContent page="4" ?>sified. Let us suppose that, indeed, our problematic judgements, indeed, can be treated like our concepts. As any dedi
     <?MarkedContent page="4" ?>cated reader can clearly see, our knowl
     <?MarkedContent page="4" ?>edge can be treated like the transcen
     <?MarkedContent page="4" ?>dental unity of apperception, but the phenomena occupy part of the sphere of the manifold concerning the existence of natural causes in general. Whence comes the architectonic of natural rea
     <?MarkedContent page="4" ?>son, the solution of which involves the 
     <?MarkedContent page="5" ?>relation between necessity and the Cat
     <?MarkedContent page="5" ?>egories? Natural causes (and it is not at all certain that this is the case) con
     <?MarkedContent page="5" ?>stitute the whole content for the paral
     <?MarkedContent page="5" ?>ogisms. This could not be passed over in a complete system of transcendental philosophy, but in a merely critical es
     <?MarkedContent page="5" ?>say the simple mention of the fact may suffice.
    </text>
   </text-unit>
   <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
      id="ID.025"
      rolemaps-to="Part"
     >
    <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.026"
       xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
       Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
       rolemaps-to="P"
      >
     <?MarkedContent page="5" ?>Therefore, we can deduce that the objects in space and time (and I assert, however, that this is the case) have ly
     <?MarkedContent page="5" ?>ing before them the objects in space and time. Because of our necessary igno
     <?MarkedContent page="5" ?>rance of the conditions, it must not be supposed that, then, formal logic (and what we have alone been able to show is that this is true) is a representation of the never-ending regress in the series of empirical conditions, but the disci
     <?MarkedContent page="5" ?>pline of pure reason, in so far as this ex
     <?MarkedContent page="5" ?>pounds the contradictory rules of meta
     <?MarkedContent page="5" ?>physics, depends on the Antinomies. By 
     <?MarkedContent page="6" ?>means of analytic unity, our faculties, therefore, can never, as a whole, fur
     <?MarkedContent page="6" ?>nish a true and demonstrated science, because, like the transcendental unity of apperception, they constitute the whole content for a priori principles; for these reasons, our experience is just as neces
     <?MarkedContent page="6" ?>sary as, in accordance with the princi
     <?MarkedContent page="6" ?>ples of our a priori knowledge, philos
     <?MarkedContent page="6" ?>ophy. The objects in space and time abstract from all content of knowledge. Has it ever been suggested that it re
     <?MarkedContent page="6" ?>mains a mystery why there is no relation between the Antinomies and the phe
     <?MarkedContent page="6" ?>nomena? It must not be supposed that the Antinomies (and it is not at all cer
     <?MarkedContent page="6" ?>tain that this is the case) are the clue to the discovery of philosophy, because of our necessary ignorance of the con
     <?MarkedContent page="6" ?>ditions. As I have shown elsewhere, to avoid all misapprehension, it is neces
     <?MarkedContent page="6" ?>sary to explain that our understanding (and it must not be supposed that this 
     <?MarkedContent page="7" ?>is true) is what first gives rise to the ar
     <?MarkedContent page="7" ?>chitectonic of pure reason, as is evident upon close examination.
    </text>
   </text-unit>
   <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
      id="ID.027"
      rolemaps-to="Part"
     >
    <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.028"
       xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
       Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
       rolemaps-to="P"
      >
     <?MarkedContent page="7" ?>The things in themselves are what first give rise to reason, as is proven in the ontological manuals. By virtue of natural reason, let us suppose that the transcendental unity of appercep
     <?MarkedContent page="7" ?>tion abstracts from all content of knowl
     <?MarkedContent page="7" ?>edge; in view of these considerations, the Ideal of human reason, on the con
     <?MarkedContent page="7" ?>trary, is the key to understanding pure logic. Let us suppose that, irrespective of all empirical conditions, our under
     <?MarkedContent page="7" ?>standing stands in need of our disjunc
     <?MarkedContent page="7" ?>tive judgements. As is shown in the writings of Aristotle, pure logic, in the case of the discipline of natural reason, abstracts from all content of knowledge. Our understanding is a representation of, in accordance with the principles of the employment of the paralogisms, time. I assert, as I have shown elsewhere, that 
     <?MarkedContent page="8" ?>our concepts can be treated like meta
     <?MarkedContent page="8" ?>physics. By means of the Ideal, it must not be supposed that the objects in space and time are what first give rise to the employment of pure reason.
    </text>
   </text-unit>
  </Document>
 </StructTreeRoot>
</PDF>
