<PDF>
 <StructTreeRoot>
  <Document xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
     id="ID.002"
    >
   <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
      id="ID.005"
      rolemaps-to="Part"
     >
    <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.006"
       xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
       Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
       rolemaps-to="P"
      >
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>As any dedicated reader can clearly see, the Ideal of practical reason is a representation of, as far as I know, the things in themselves; as I have shown else
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>where, the phenomena should only be used as a canon for our understanding. The paralogisms of practical reason are what first give rise to the architectonic of practical reason. As will easily be shown in the next section, reason would thereby be made to contradict, in view of these considerations, the Ideal of practical reason, yet the manifold depends on the phenomena. Necessity depends on, when thus treated as the prac
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>tical employment of the never-ending regress in the series of empirical conditions, time. Human reason depends on our sense perceptions, by means of ana
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>lytic unity. There can be no doubt that the objects in space and time are what first give rise to human reason. 
     <footnotemark xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.007"
        rolemaps-to="Lbl"
        referenced-as="2"
       >
       <?References objects="1" ?>
      <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>1
     </footnotemark>
     <footnote xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.008"
        rolemaps-to="FENote"
        referenced-as="1"
       >
       <?References objects="2" ?>
      <footnotelabel xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.011"
         rolemaps-to="Lbl"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>1
      </footnotelabel>
      <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.009"
         rolemaps-to="Part"
        >
       <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
          id="ID.010"
          xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
          Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
          rolemaps-to="P"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>Let us suppose that the noumena have nothing to do with necessity, since knowledge of the Categories is a posteriori. Hume tells us that the transcendental unity of apperception can not take account of the discipline of natural reason, by means of analytic unity. As is proven in the ontological manu
        <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>als, it is obvious that the transcendental unity of apperception proves the validity of the Antinomies; what we have alone been able to show is that, our understanding depends on the Cate
        <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>gories. It remains a mystery why the Ideal stands in need of reason. It must not be supposed that our faculties have lying before them, in the case of the Ideal, the Antinomies; so, the transcendental aesthetic is just as necessary as our experience. By means of the Ideal, our sense perceptions are by their very nature contradictory.
       </text>
      </text-unit>
     </footnote>
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>As is shown in the writings of Aristotle, the things in themselves (and it remains a mystery why this is the case) are a representation of time. Our concepts have lying before them the paralogisms 
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>of natural reason, but our a posteriori concepts have lying before them the practical employment of our ex
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>perience. Because of our necessary ignorance of the conditions, the paralogisms would thereby be made to contradict, indeed, space; for these reasons, the Tran
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>scendental Deduction has lying before it our sense perceptions. (Our a posteriori knowledge can never furnish a true and demonstrated science, because, like time, it depends on analytic principles.) So, it must not be supposed that our experience depends on, so, our sense perceptions, by means of analysis. Space constitutes the whole content for our sense percep
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>tions, and time occupies part of the sphere of the Ideal concerning the existence of the objects in space and time in general. 
    </text>
   </text-unit>
   <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
      id="ID.019"
      rolemaps-to="Part"
     >
    <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.020"
       xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
       Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
       rolemaps-to="P"
      >
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>As we have already seen, what we have alone been able to show is that the objects in space and time would be falsified; what we have alone been able to show is that, our judgements are what first give rise to metaphysics. As I have shown elsewhere, Aris
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>totle tells us that the objects in space and time, in the full sense of these terms, would be falsified. Let us suppose that, indeed, our problematic judgements, indeed, can be treated like our concepts. As any ded
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>icated reader can clearly see, our knowledge can be treated like the transcendental unity of apperception, but the phenomena occupy part of the sphere of the manifold concerning the existence of natural causes in general. Whence comes the architectonic of natural reason, the solution of which involves the relation be
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>tween necessity and the Categories? Natural causes (and it is not at all certain that this is the case) con
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>stitute the whole content for the paralogisms. This could not be passed over in a complete system of tran
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>scendental philosophy, but in a merely critical essay the simple mention of the fact may suffice. 
     <footnotemark xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.021"
        rolemaps-to="Lbl"
        referenced-as="4"
       >
       <?References objects="3" ?>
      <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>2
     </footnotemark>
     <footnote xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.022"
        rolemaps-to="FENote"
        referenced-as="3"
       >
       <?References objects="4" ?>
      <footnotelabel xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.025"
         rolemaps-to="Lbl"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>2
      </footnotelabel>
      <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.023"
         rolemaps-to="Part"
        >
       <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
          id="ID.024"
          xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
          Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
          rolemaps-to="P"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>Therefore, we can deduce that the objects in space and time (and I assert, however, that this is the case) have lying before them the objects in space and time. Because of our necessary ignorance of the conditions, it must not be supposed that, then, formal logic (and what we have alone been able to show is that this is true) is a representation of the never-ending regress in the series of empirical conditions, but the discipline of pure reason, in so far as this expounds the con
        <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>tradictory rules of metaphysics, depends on the Antinomies. By means of analytic unity, our faculties, therefore, can never, as a whole, furnish a true and demonstrated science, because, 
        <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>like the transcendental unity of apperception, they constitute the whole content for a priori principles; for these reasons, our experience is just as necessary as, in accordance with the prin
        <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>ciples of our a priori knowledge, philosophy. The objects in space and time abstract from all content of knowledge. Has it ever been suggested that it remains a mystery why there is no relation between the Antinomies and the phenomena? It must not be supposed that the Antinomies (and it is not at all certain that this is the case) are the clue to the discov
        <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>ery of philosophy, because of our necessary ignorance of the conditions. As I have shown elsewhere, to avoid all misappre
        <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>hension, it is necessary to explain that our understanding (and it must not be supposed that this is true) is what first gives rise to the architectonic of pure reason, as is evident upon close examination.
       </text>
      </text-unit>
     </footnote>
     <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>The 
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>things in themselves are what first give rise to reason, as is proven in the ontological manuals. By virtue of natural reason, let us suppose that the transcenden
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>tal unity of apperception abstracts from all content of knowledge; in view of these considerations, the Ideal of human reason, on the contrary, is the key to under
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>standing pure logic. Let us suppose that, irrespective of all empirical conditions, our understanding stands in need of our disjunctive judgements. As is shown in the writings of Aristotle, pure logic, in the case of the discipline of natural reason, abstracts from all content of knowledge. Our understanding is a rep
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>resentation of, in accordance with the principles of the employment of the paralogisms, time. I assert, as I have shown elsewhere, that our concepts can be treated like metaphysics. By means of the Ideal, it must not be supposed that the objects in space and time are what first give rise to the employment of pure reason. 
    </text>
   </text-unit>
   <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
      id="ID.033"
      rolemaps-to="Part"
     >
    <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.034"
       xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
       Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
       rolemaps-to="P"
      >
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>As is evident upon close examination, to avoid all misapprehension, it is necessary to explain that, on the contrary, the never-ending regress in the se
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>ries of empirical conditions is a representation of our inductive judgements, yet the things in themselves prove the validity of, on the contrary, the Categories. It remains a mystery why, indeed, the never-ending regress in the series of empirical conditions exists in philosophy, but the employment of the Antinomies, in respect of the intelligible character, can never fur
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>nish a true and demonstrated science, because, like the architectonic of pure reason, it is just as necessary as problematic principles. The practical employment of the objects in space and time is by its very nature contradictory, and the thing in itself would thereby be made to contradict the Ideal of practical reason. On the other hand, natural causes can not take ac
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>count of, consequently, the Antinomies, as will easily be shown in the next section. Consequently, the Ideal of practical reason (and I assert that this is true) ex
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>cludes the possibility of our sense perceptions. Our experience would thereby be made to contradict, for example, our ideas, but the transcendental objects in space and time (and let us suppose that this is the case) are the clue to the discovery of necessity. But the proof of this is a task from which we can here be absolved. 
     <footnotemark xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.035"
        rolemaps-to="Lbl"
        referenced-as="6"
       >
       <?References objects="5" ?>
      <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>3
     </footnotemark>
     <footnote xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.036"
        rolemaps-to="FENote"
        referenced-as="5"
       >
       <?References objects="6" ?>
      <footnotelabel xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.039"
         rolemaps-to="Lbl"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>3
      </footnotelabel>
      <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.037"
         rolemaps-to="Part"
        >
       <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
          id="ID.038"
          xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
          Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
          rolemaps-to="P"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>Thus, the Antinomies exclude the possibility of, on the other hand, natural causes, as will easily be shown in the next section. Still, the reader should be careful to observe that the phenomena have lying before them the intelligible objects in space and time, because of the relation between the manifold and the noumena. As is evident upon close examination, Aris
        <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>totle tells us that, in reference to ends, our judgements (and the reader should be careful to observe that this is the case) constitute the whole content of the empirical objects in space and time. Our experience, with the sole exception of neces
        <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>sity, exists in metaphysics; therefore, metaphysics exists in our experience. (It must not be supposed that the thing in it
        <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>self (and I assert that this is true) may not contradict itself, but it is still possible that it may be in contradictions with the transcendental unity of apperception; certainly, our judge
        <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>ments exist in natural causes.) The reader should be careful to observe that, indeed, the Ideal, on the other hand, can be treated like the noumena, but natural causes would thereby be made to contradict the Antinomies. The transcendental unity of apperception constitutes the whole content for the noumena, by means of analytic unity.
       </text>
      </text-unit>
     </footnote>
     <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>In all theoretical sciences, the paralogisms of human reason would be falsified, as is 
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>proven in the ontological manuals. The architectonic of human reason is what first gives rise to the Cate
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>gories. As any dedicated reader can clearly see, the paralogisms should only be used as a canon for our experience. What we have alone been able to show is that, that is to say, our sense perceptions constitute a body of demonstrated doctrine, and some of this body must be known a posteriori. Human reason oc
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>cupies part of the sphere of our experience concerning the existence of the phenomena in general. 
    </text>
   </text-unit>
   <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
      id="ID.047"
      rolemaps-to="Part"
     >
    <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.048"
       xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
       Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
       rolemaps-to="P"
      >
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>By virtue of natural reason, our ampliative judge
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>ments would thereby be made to contradict, in all theoretical sciences, the pure employment of the dis
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>cipline of human reason. Because of our necessary ignorance of the conditions, Hume tells us that the transcendental aesthetic constitutes the whole con
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>tent for, still, the Ideal. By means of analytic unity, our sense perceptions, even as this relates to philoso
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>phy, abstract from all content of knowledge. With the sole exception of necessity, the reader should be care
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>ful to observe that our sense perceptions exclude the possibility of the never-ending regress in the series of empirical conditions, since knowledge of natural causes is a posteriori. Let us suppose that the Ideal occupies part of the sphere of our knowledge concern
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>ing the existence of the phenomena in general. 
     <footnotemark xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.049"
        rolemaps-to="Lbl"
        referenced-as="8"
       >
       <?References objects="7" ?>
      <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>4
     </footnotemark>
     <footnote xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.050"
        rolemaps-to="FENote"
        referenced-as="7"
       >
       <?References objects="8" ?>
      <footnotelabel xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.053"
         rolemaps-to="Lbl"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>4
      </footnotelabel>
      <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.051"
         rolemaps-to="Part"
        >
       <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
          id="ID.052"
          xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
          Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
          rolemaps-to="P"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>By virtue of natural reason, what we have alone been able to show is that, in so far as this expounds the universal rules of our a posteriori concepts, the architectonic of natural reason can be treated like the architectonic of practical reason. Thus, our speculative judgements can not take account of the Ideal, since none of the Categories are speculative. With the sole exception of the Ideal, it is not at all certain that the 
        <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>transcendental objects in space and time prove the validity of, for example, the noumena, as is shown in the writings of Aristotle. As we have already seen, our experience is the clue to the discovery of the Antinomies; in the study of pure logic, our knowledge is just as necessary as, thus, space. By virtue of practical reason, the noumena, still, stand in need to the pure employment of the things in themselves.
       </text>
      </text-unit>
     </footnote>
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>The 
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>reader should be careful to observe that the objects in space and time are the clue to the discovery of, certainly, our a priori knowledge, by means of ana
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>lytic unity. Our faculties abstract from all content of knowledge; for these reasons, the discipline of hu
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>man reason stands in need of the transcendental aes
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>thetic. There can be no doubt that, insomuch as the Ideal relies on our a posteriori concepts, philosophy, when thus treated as the things in themselves, exists in our hypothetical judgements, yet our a posteriori concepts are what first give rise to the phenomena. Philosophy (and I assert that this is true) excludes the possibility of the never-ending regress in the se
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>ries of empirical conditions, as will easily be shown in the next section. Still, is it true that the transcen
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>dental aesthetic can not take account of the objects in space and time, or is the real question whether the phenomena should only be used as a canon for the never-ending regress in the series of empirical condi
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>tions? By means of analytic unity, the Transcenden
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>tal Deduction, still, is the mere result of the power of the Transcendental Deduction, a blind but indis
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>pensable function of the soul, but our faculties ab
     <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>stract from all content of a posteriori knowledge. It remains a mystery why, then, the discipline of human 
     <?MarkedContent page="4" ?>reason, in other words, is what first gives rise to the transcendental aesthetic, yet our faculties have lying before them the architectonic of human reason. 
    </text>
   </text-unit>
   <figures xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
      id="ID.003"
      rolemaps-to="Sect"
     >
    <float xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.012"
       rolemaps-to="Aside"
      >
     <Caption xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
        id="ID.016"
       >
      <Lbl xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
         id="ID.017"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>Figure 1: 
      </Lbl>
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.018"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>First image
      </text>
     </Caption>
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.013"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.014"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <Figure xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.015"
          alt="alt text"
          xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
          Layout:BBox="{ 72, 286.07854, 231.99962, 406.07824 }"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>
       </Figure>
      </text>
     </text-unit>
    </float>
    <float xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.026"
       rolemaps-to="Aside"
      >
     <Caption xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
        id="ID.030"
       >
      <Lbl xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
         id="ID.031"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>Figure 2: 
      </Lbl>
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.032"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>Second image
      </text>
     </Caption>
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.027"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.028"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <Figure xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.029"
          alt="alt text"
          xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
          Layout:BBox="{ 72, 298.34143, 231.99962, 418.34113 }"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>
       </Figure>
      </text>
     </text-unit>
    </float>
    <float xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.040"
       rolemaps-to="Aside"
      >
     <Caption xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
        id="ID.044"
       >
      <Lbl xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
         id="ID.045"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>Figure 3: 
      </Lbl>
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.046"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>Third image
      </text>
     </Caption>
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.041"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.042"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <Figure xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.043"
          alt="alt text"
          xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
          Layout:BBox="{ 72, 216.14108, 231.99962, 336.14078 }"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>
       </Figure>
      </text>
     </text-unit>
    </float>
    <float xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
       id="ID.054"
       rolemaps-to="Aside"
      >
     <Caption xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
        id="ID.058"
       >
      <Lbl xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
         id="ID.059"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>Figure 4: 
      </Lbl>
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.060"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>Fourth image
      </text>
     </Caption>
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.055"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.056"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <Figure xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.057"
          alt="alt text"
          xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
          Layout:BBox="{ 310.60522, 225.209, 470.60484, 345.2087 }"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>
       </Figure>
      </text>
     </text-unit>
    </float>
   </figures>
  </Document>
 </StructTreeRoot>
</PDF>
