<PDF>
 <StructTreeRoot>
  <Document xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
     id="ID.0002"
    >
   <Sect xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
      id="ID.0005"
     >
    <chapter xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/book"
       id="ID.0006"
       title="Book 1"
       rolemaps-to="H1"
      >
     <Span xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
        id="ID.0007"
        xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
        Layout:TextAlign="Start"
       >
      <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>Book 1
     </Span>
    </chapter>
    <Sect xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
       id="ID.0008"
      >
     <section xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/book"
        id="ID.0009"
        title="The Argument"
        rolemaps-to="H2"
       >
      <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>The Argument
     </section>
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.0010"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.0011"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>
       <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.0012"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>
        <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
           id="ID.0013"
          >
         <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>This first Book proposes, first in brief, the whole Subject
        </Em>
        <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>, Mans disobedience,and the loss thereupon of Paradise wherein he was plac’t:
        <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
           id="ID.0014"
          >
         <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>Then touches
        </Em>
        <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>theprime cause of his fall, the Serpent, or rather Satan in the Serpent; who revoltingfrom God, and drawing to his side many Legions of Angels, was by the commandof God driven out of Heaven with all his Crew into the great Deep.
        <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
           id="ID.0015"
          >
         <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>Which actionpast over, the Poem hasts into the midst of things
        </Em>
        <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>, presenting Satan with hisAngels now fallen into Hell,
        <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
           id="ID.0016"
          >
         <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>describ’d here
        </Em>
        <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>, not in the Center
        <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
           id="ID.0017"
          >
         <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>(for Heaven andEarth may be suppos’d as yet not made, certainly not yet accurst)
        </Em>
        <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>but in a placeof utter darkness, fitliest call’d
        <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
           id="ID.0018"
          >
         <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>Chaos:
        </Em>
        <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>Here
        <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
           id="ID.0019"
          >
         <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>Satan
        </Em>
        <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>with his Angels lying on theburning Lake, thunder-struck and astonisht, after a certain space recovers, asfrom confusion, calls up him who next in Order and Dignity lay by him; theyconfer of thir miserable fall.
        <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
           id="ID.0020"
          >
         <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>Satan
        </Em>
        <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>awakens all his Legions, who lay till thenin the same manner confounded; They rise, thir Numbers, array of Battel, thirchief Leaders nam’d, according to the Idols known afterwards in
        <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
           id="ID.0021"
          >
         <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>Canaan
        </Em>
        <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>andthe Countries adjoyning. To these
        <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
           id="ID.0022"
          >
         <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>Satan
        </Em>
        <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>directs his Speech, comforts them withhope yet of regaining Heaven, but tells them lastly of a new World and newkind of Creature to be created, according to an ancient Prophesie or report inHeaven;
        <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
           id="ID.0023"
          >
         <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>for that Angels were long before this visible Creation, was the opinionof many ancient Fathers
        </Em>
        <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>. To find out the truth of this Prophesie, and whatto determin thereon he refers to a full Councel. What his Associates thenceattempt.
        <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
           id="ID.0024"
          >
         <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>Pandemonium
        </Em>
        <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>the Palace of Satan rises, suddenly built out of theDeep: The infernal Peers there sit in Councel.
       </Em>
       <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>
      </text>
     </text-unit>
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.0025"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.0026"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>Of Mans First Disobedience, and the FruitOf that Forbidden Tree, whose mortal tastBrought Death into the World, and all our woe,With loss of
       <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.0027"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>Eden
       </Em>
       <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>, till one greater ManRestore us, and regain the blissful Seat,Sing Heav’nly Muse, that on the secret topOf
       <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.0028"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>Oreb
       </Em>
       <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>, or of
       <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.0029"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>Sinai
       </Em>
       <?MarkedContent page="1" ?>, didst inspire
       <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>That Shepherd, who first taught the chosen Seed,In the Beginning how the Heav’ns and EarthRose out of Chaos: Or if
       <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.0030"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>Sion
       </Em>
       <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>HillDelight thee more, and
       <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.0031"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>Siloa’s Brook
       </Em>
       <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>that flow’dFast by the Oracle of God; I thenceInvoke thy aid to my adventrous Song,That with no middle flight intends to soarAbove th’ Aonian Mount, while it pursuesThings unattempted yet in Prose or Rhime.And chiefly Thou O Spirit, that dost preferBefore all Temples th’ upright heart and pure,Instruct me, for Thou know’st; Thou from the firstWast present, and with mighty wings outspreadDove-like satst brooding on the vast AbyssAnd mad’st it pregnant: What in me is darkIllumin, what is low raise and support;That to the highth of this great ArgumentI may assert Eternal Providence,And justifie the wayes of God to men.
      </text>
     </text-unit>
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.0032"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.0033"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="3" ?>Say first, for Heav’n hides nothing from thy viewNor the deep Tract of Hell, say first what causeMov’d our Grand Parents in that happy State,Favour’d of Heav’n so highly, to fall offFrom thir Creator, and transgress his WillFor one restraint, Lords of the World besides?Who first seduc’d them to that foul revolt?Th’ infernal Serpent; he it was, whose guileStird up with Envy and Revenge, deceiv’dThe Mother of Mankind, what time his PrideHad cast him out from Heav’n, with all his HostOf Rebel Angels, by whose aid aspiringTo set himself in Glory above his Peers,He trusted to have equal’d the most High,If he oppos’d; and with ambitious aimAgainst the Throne and Monarchy of GodRais’d impious War in Heav’n and Battel proudWith vain attempt. Him the Almighty PowerHurld headlong flaming from th’ Ethereal SkieWith hideous ruine and combustion downTo bottomless perdition, there to dwellIn Adamantine Chains and penal Fire,Who durst defie th’ Omnipotent to Arms.Nine times the Space that measures Day and NightTo mortal men, he with his horrid crewLay vanquisht, rowling in the fiery Gulfe
       <?MarkedContent page="5" ?>Confounded though immortal: But his doomReserv’d him to more wrath; for now the thoughtBoth of lost happiness and lasting painTorments him; round he throws his baleful eyesThat witness’d huge affliction and dismayMixt with obdurate pride and stedfast hate:At once as far as Angels kenn he viewsThe dismal Situation waste and wilde,A Dungeon horrible, on all sides roundAs one great Furnace flam’d, yet from those flamesNo light, but rather darkness visibleServ’d onely to discover sights of woe,Regions of sorrow, doleful shades, where peaceAnd rest can never dwell, hope never comesThat comes to all; but torture without endStill urges, and a fiery Deluge, fedWith ever-burning Sulphur unconsum’d:Such place Eternal Justice had prepar’dFor those rebellious, here thir Prison ordain’dIn utter darkness, and thir portion setAs far remov’d from God and light of Heav’nAs from the Center thrice to th’ utmost Pole.O how unlike the place from whence they fell!There the companions of his fall, o’rewhelm’dWith Floods and Whirlwinds of tempestuous fire,He soon discerns, and weltring by his sideOne next himself in power, and next in crime,Long after known in Palestine, and nam’dBeelzebub. To whom th’ Arch-Enemy,And thence in Heav’n call’d Satan, with bold wordsBreaking the horrid silence thus began.
      </text>
     </text-unit>
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.0034"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.0035"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>
       <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.0036"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>chosen Seed
       </Em>
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>: The people of Israel. See Exodus 19-20.
      </text>
     </text-unit>
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.0037"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.0038"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>
       <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.0039"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>In the Beginning
       </Em>
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>: The opening words of both Genesis (Geneva) and the Gospel of John(Geneva).
      </text>
     </text-unit>
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.0040"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.0041"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>
       <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.0042"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>out of Chaos
       </Em>
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>: One of Milton’s several heterodox positions. Orthodoxy held that Godcreated everything ex nihilo, out of nothing (the “void” of Genesis 1:2; See Calvin’sCommentary on Genesis). Milton borrows the concept of chaos, or unformed matter, fromHesiod and Platonic philosophy (especially the Timaeus 53b). Milton was also a monist,holding that all things were created out of God; see book 5.468–490.
      </text>
     </text-unit>
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.0043"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.0044"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>
       <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.0045"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>
        <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
           id="ID.0046"
          >
         <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>Sion
        </Em>
        <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>
       </Em>
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>: To the haunts of the classical muses near the Castalian spring on Mt. Parnassus,Milton prefers to claim Mt. Sion and its brooks Kidron and Siloa, a kind of biblicallyauthorized Parnassus.
      </text>
     </text-unit>
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.0047"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.0048"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>
       <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.0049"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>
        <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
           id="ID.0050"
          >
         <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>Siloa’s Brook
        </Em>
        <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>
       </Em>
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>: “The Pool of Siloam (Hebrew: Breikhat Hashiloah) is a rock-cut pool on thesouthern slope of the City of David, the original site of Jerusalem, located outside the wallsof the Old City to the southeast. The pool was fed by the waters of the Gihon Spring,carried there by two aqueducts” (Wikipedia, “Pool of Siloam.”)
      </text>
     </text-unit>
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.0051"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.0052"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>
       <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.0053"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>adventrous Song
       </Em>
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>: Note the similarities between Milton’s opening and the opening lines ofVirgil’s Aeneid and of Homer’s Odyssey. Milton wants not only to compare his project tothe ancient epics, but also himself to those poets and his main character, Adam, to theircelebrated heroes. All of these comparisons raise interesting and complicated questions ofauthority, heroism, and nationalism in art.
      </text>
     </text-unit>
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.0054"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.0055"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>
       <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.0056"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>Aonian Mount
       </Em>
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>: Mt. Helicon, in Aonia, sacred to the classical muses.
      </text>
     </text-unit>
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.0057"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.0058"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>
       <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.0059"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>in Prose or Rhime
       </Em>
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>: The line ironically (maybe even sarcastically?) recalls the stanza 2 ofcanto 1 of Ariosto’s Orlando Furioso.
      </text>
     </text-unit>
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.0060"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.0061"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>
       <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.0062"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>Dove-like
       </Em>
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>: The Holy Spirit appears as a dove in John 1: 32. See also Paradise Regain’d1.30-1.
      </text>
     </text-unit>
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.0063"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.0064"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>
       <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.0065"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>brooding on the vast Abyss
       </Em>
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>: Milton’s “brooding” is a better translation of the Hebrew thanthe familiar “moved upon the face of the waters” of the Authorized version of Genesis 1:2.
      </text>
     </text-unit>
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.0066"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.0067"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>
       <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.0068"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>pregnant
       </Em>
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>: Milton invites us to imagine the Holy Spirit copulating with the unformed matterof Chaos (“the vast Abyss”). In Milton’s monism, distinctions between spirit and matter arenot absolute.
      </text>
     </text-unit>
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.0069"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.0070"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>
       <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.0071"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>Say first
       </Em>
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>: Compare this with Homer’s invocation to the muse in the Iliad 1.8.
      </text>
     </text-unit>
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.0072"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.0073"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>
       <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.0074"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>one restraint
       </Em>
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>: That is, the single injunction against eating from the tree of the knowledge ofgood and evil (Genesis 2: 17).
      </text>
     </text-unit>
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.0075"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.0076"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>
       <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.0077"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>Lords of the World
       </Em>
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>: According to Genesis 1:28, human beings were created to “havedominion” over the rest of creation.
      </text>
     </text-unit>
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.0078"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.0079"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>
       <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.0080"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>Hurld headlong flaming
       </Em>
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>: This description recalls Pieter Bruegel’s Fall of the Rebel Angels(about 1562). See also William Blake’s 1808 watercolor illustration of the rebel angels’ fall(told by Raphael at 6.864-66).
      </text>
     </text-unit>
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.0081"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.0082"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>
       <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.0083"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>Adamantine
       </Em>
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>: Unbreakable, rocklike.
      </text>
     </text-unit>
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.0084"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.0085"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>
       <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.0086"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>Nine times the Space
       </Em>
       <?MarkedContent page="2" ?>: In Hesiod’s Theogony 664-735, the Titans take a similar fall at thehands of Zeus. Interestingly, though Milton alludes to the fall of the Titans here, he likenstheir nine-day fall, not to the fall of the rebel angels, but to the time they spent lyingvanquished on the fiery gulf after their fall. Raphael, in book 6, line 871, however, tellsAdam that the rebel angels fell for “Nine dayes”.
      </text>
     </text-unit>
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.0087"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.0088"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="4" ?>
       <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.0089"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="4" ?>kenn
       </Em>
       <?MarkedContent page="4" ?>: Range, which in the case of angels must be presumed to be nearly limitless.
      </text>
     </text-unit>
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.0090"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.0091"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="4" ?>
       <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.0092"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="4" ?>hope never comes
       </Em>
       <?MarkedContent page="4" ?>: A deliberate echo of Dante’s Inferno 3.9: “All hope abandon ye who enterhere.”
      </text>
     </text-unit>
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.0093"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.0094"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="4" ?>
       <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.0095"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="4" ?>thir
       </Em>
       <?MarkedContent page="4" ?>: Their. Milton’s preferred spelling was “thir,” and Flannagan reports that “their” waschanged to “thir” in later stages of the 1674 edition. The same is true of line 499 and otherlines.
      </text>
     </text-unit>
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.0096"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.0097"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="4" ?>
       <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.0098"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="4" ?>from the Center thrice to th’ utmost Pole
       </Em>
       <?MarkedContent page="4" ?>: Milton asks us to refer to the Ptolemaic model ofthe universe with the earth at the center of nine concentric spheres. On Milton’s cosmology,Ptolemaic or Copernican, see also book 8. 119-68.
      </text>
     </text-unit>
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.0099"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.0100"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="4" ?>
       <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.0101"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="4" ?>Beelzebub
       </Em>
       <?MarkedContent page="4" ?>: “God of the flies” or “Chief of the devils.” See Matthew 10: 25, Mark 3: 22, andLuke 11: 15. See also Christopher Marlowe’s Doctor Faustus and Burton’s Anatomy ofMelancholy 1.2.1-2; see also the Wikipedia entry.
      </text>
     </text-unit>
     <text-unit xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
        id="ID.0102"
        rolemaps-to="Part"
       >
      <text xmlns="https://www.latex-project.org/ns/dflt"
         id="ID.0103"
         xmlns:Layout="http://iso.org/pdf/ssn/Layout"
         Layout:TextAlign="Justify"
         rolemaps-to="P"
        >
       <?MarkedContent page="4" ?>
       <Em xmlns="http://iso.org/pdf2/ssn"
          id="ID.0104"
         >
        <?MarkedContent page="4" ?>call’d Satan
       </Em>
       <?MarkedContent page="4" ?>: Originally Lucifer, “bringer of light,” his name in heaven is changed to Satan,“enemy.”
      </text>
     </text-unit>
    </Sect>
   </Sect>
  </Document>
 </StructTreeRoot>
</PDF>
